Yaeli sheinberger

yaeli8454@gmail.com

0548410992

Q Jerusalem

0548410992

Q Jerusalem

Education

Computer Science (B.Sc) 2020 - Oct 2024

Bachelor's student at the Open University.

Specializes in business management and 2016 - 2020

accounting.

High School, Ministry of Education.

Employment

Course guidance for learning Python

Present

Guiding high school students the language studies from 0 prior knowledge, to mastering the language and submitting a final project. In the PyCharm workspace.

Secretary at Mayanot College

Present

Temporary work at the same time as studies,

Management in the college offices, registrations, information, collection of funds.

Extracurricular activities

Drachi Miriam Association at Shaare Zedek

2021 - 2023

Hospital

Supporting the sick families by showing interest and distributing food.

Ezer mizion

Caring for children with special needs.

Jan 2023 - Jul 2023

Mentor for elementary school girls who have difficulty in studies.

projects and achievements

Salas mentoring project for students

Chosen based on academic excellence to guide female students in the first and second year of the courses:

* Introduction to computer science and the Java language A. * Differential and integral calculus B.

The hackathon project

Website development for a babysitter matching service. Made in Java language, including design, PoC development.

Personal details

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/yaelisheinberger

profile

Third-year computer science student, with excellent interpersonal skills, high capacity for self-learning, experienced in working under pressure, high responsibility and work ethic, serious, striving for excellence, motivated to learn and know more, passionate about researching and solving problems.

skills

Java, c, Python, SQL

Among the courses studied

Differential and integral calculus A and B, introduction to computer science and the Java language A and B, advanced programming in the Java language, data structures and an introduction to algorithms, systems programming laboratory, linear algebra for science students, numerical systems, database systems, porthole for mathematics, discrete mathematics, automata and formal languages, English.

Languages

Hebrew Native language English High level